thejobportal.in 2014-12-02

# Privacy Policy | thejobportal

We, at [www.thejobportal.in](http://www.thejobportal.in/), have set the following Privacy Policy for the general users/ Third Parties of this website. By usage of any service or product on the website, you hereby agree to the terms and conditions given below as set out herein and those that are not specifically mentioned which are subject to the general norms of usage.

We, at “The Job Portal”, are committed to your online privacy and to protect any personal information you share with us.

Any information that may be used to identify an individual, including Name, Phone Number, Residential Address, E-mail address or any other contact information is protected by the website unless a user permits us to show the information publicly. If you don not wish to reveal any information, you can visit [www.thejobportal.in](http://www.thejobportal.in/) web pages confidentially or without revealing any personal information.

We take diligent care to protect all the information provided by a user in every manner, despite which we shall not be liable for the loss of any data or information provided by you. Any dispute which may arise out of or in connection with

(i)                 Any legal relationship between The Job Portal and you which is related directly or indirectly to this website,

(ii)               The terms and conditions,

(iii)             Use of the website shall be governed by the Indian Laws and the competent court in India shall have exclusive jurisdiction to settle any such disputes.

The information may be collected through various sources like

**1.   _Facebook Login_**

You may connect to The Job Portal using Facebook to open or access your account. We may use your Facebook information to link the App to your existing account, if you have one. Your information is used to maintain your account, to associate your Profile, to provide you access to restricted content and to communicate with you.

Your use of Facebook in general and your relationship with Facebook are subject to Facebook's own Data Use Policy, Statement of Rights and Responsibilities, Platform Principles and other published policies. This App does not control or is not responsible for Facebook's processing of your information. We strongly recommend that you carefully review and familiarize yourself with all Facebook's statements, policies and principles.

**2.   _Via. Technology- Cookies_**

Some of our web pages utilize **"cookies"** and other tracking technologies. A **"cookie"** is a small text file used to collect information about a website’s activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to remind personal information previously indicated by the user of a website. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether to accept them or not and how to remove the same. 

You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies on your browser. Please note that if you choose to erase or block cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the website each time you visit the website.

**3.   _Other Sources_**

We may receive your Personal Information from outside the website, such as telephone, fax, mail, or from third parties that provide services to us. We may add this information to the already available information, i.e., the information provided by you to access our website.

**4. _Posting Reviews/ Interviews_**

One of the purposes of the Services is for Members to share employment-related information with other Users. Therefore, any information (including any Personal Information that you may choose to provide, excluding your registration details) that you choose to post on the website may be made available to other Users of the Services. We may provide you with the ability to anonymously post certain comments in which case we will not include your contact information (such as name, phone number, email address or postal address) on the website along with such comments.

Please note that for any information that you post on the website, especially for the information where you wish to keep your identity hidden, your contact information will be available only to us on our internal records.

**_THIRD PARTIES/COMPANIES_**

We ensure maximum security standards to protect the users’ data against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. 

The third parties’ data usually contains:-

·         About the Company

·         Contact Information

·         Addresses

·         Employees/ Owner Information

·         Available Jobs

This information is freely available on our website and we don’t sell this information to any external party or any user of [www.thejobportal.in](http://www.thejobportal.in/).

We reserve the rights to modify this statement at any time, so please review it frequently. We may make material changes to this policy without any prior notice in the form of display on the website, your e-mail inbox or your phone.
